[Applause]
[Music]
this is what girls will resort to if we
ever get rid of Planned Parenthood she
died no redemption this week guys
we'll be right back lol that's Annie and
she tried to get cute in a cruise ship
stairwell but like every girl she's
unable to do anything fun if you've ever
been inside a crowded Walmart and said
I'd like to spend a solid week with
these people
then cruises are for you they depart out
of Florida and things only get less
classy from there
it's a floating nursing home there's
nothing more American than docking a
10-story food court off the coast of a
starving yet scenic third-world country
they're the perfect trip for lazy white
people who are too stupid or too racist
to learn enough Spanish to order a
margarita does your local Golden Corral
lack breathtaking ocean views try
Carnival Cruise Lines did I mention
there's a rock wall a better way to
experience Jamaica's rich ziplining
culture a cruise ship is an enormous
toilet in the middle of the
crystal-clear Caribbean do husband's
push their wives overboard or do women
jump because they married a guy who
considers a cruise a vacation when I
first laid eyes on Annie I said Danny
don't fall but it was too late that's
why I gave her a luxurious one-night
half-day trip to Hollywood where the
only cruise I want to go down on is
Penelope in this week's web Redemption
[Applause]
that's my time you have fat go get some
more salt
thank you Oh make it strong when Carlos
if 14 shows day and sadly that was the
best one you got a drink ticket yes I
got a drink ticket bunch of the cheeps
join me I'm only 17
she's only 17 attention we are now in
international waters that doesn't matter
anymore maritime law what's maritime law
it means that legally I'm allowed to
boink you I could even murder you if I
wanted which I don't were you an orphan
or did your mom name you Annie
actually my name is Ann who calls you
Annie everyone everyone were you from
South Carolina South Carolina you ever
get to that Myrtle Beach stripper
convention I've been hearing so much
about you know I haven't it's on the
bucket list though South Carolina I do
how do you feel about the Confederate
flag how many cruises have you been on I
think 16 16 why you just like them how
do you go with your family ever get to
go alone no yeah between you wanted to
go alone so you have to have a guardian
I can have anyone over 21 anyone over 21
is allowed to take a 17 year olds of
cruise yes they don't have to be related
to you I don't think so after Christmas
oh what a gift to all of us it didn't
work out now it looked like you died
right how painful was it
well I land on the railing below me okay
so that were fall they broke my fall
in my rib it broke your rib yes did you
go see the cruise ship doctor I did not
there is a cruise ship dock yes I think
so
that seems sketchy you know there's also
a morgue on a lot of cruise ships really
yeah okay hates people died on a cruise
ship they're not gonna ruin everybody's
fun they put them on ice and keep the
party going
that's true yeah I mean I don't know if
it's true I mean it does make sense it
doesn't seem like I mean cruise ships
are a lot of old people true so you know
people are dying on cruise ships they're
turning around like back to Fort
Lauderdale why did you fall when your
friends clearly told you not to fall by
the way did you hear that as you were
falling her annoying voice yes wider
voice a line so she a trucker the whole
week have you ever been on a real
vacation what do you consider a real
vacation you know a hotel land yes all
right
tell me the best story about diarrhea on
a cruise ship don't think it happened
my brother's friend them the last night
of cruise a few years ago did like throw
up all night in the bathroom so me and
my friend how'd it go sleep in the
hallway cause it smelled so bad so a
little maid woke us up in the morning
with like you can't sleep here okay I
don't know what racist accent that was
it was spot on
yeah understood what a fun drink has
fish in it did you know your friend was
a perv and upskirt videos that was a
surprise to all of us but I mean she's
always been overly friendly but I didn't
I didn't but you can't like pause it and
and see a shot no I don't think you can
like actually okay good see we're going
commando No thank God thank goodness has
anybody ever been murdered on a cruise
ship while you've been on it not that
they'd let me know do they helicopter
people off we'd like picked up people
and a little like rundown were you
scared that it was a it was pirates no
do they teach how to work the hoses to
spray the Pirates off no you get a hose
you spray him I hate to be sprayed in
the face they're like cats hi very much
so
careful you're drunk
attention passengers the buffet is down
to its last 2,000 pounds of popcorn
shrimp raised by the chef
[Music]
take me to your cabin they upgraded me
to a room 24s below sea level it's right
next to the engine on the Mexican cartel
storage deck this is best way to go I do
not new elevators
[Music]
okay are you okay are you okay Annie yes
all right was just having a flashback
I'll never let you fall
[Music]
girls no stop talking I'm almost
finished
I look like a fat Kate Winslet Amy I
don't feel so good well sure your
17-year old girl who's been drinking all
night long which I'd like to remind the
viewers at home is completely legal in
international waters maritime law
maritime law fresh air yeah it's a big
go they are no longer in international
waters okay they don't fall hey he had a
little concussion and washed ashore
where she was picked up my current
rustle and forced to mother his children
[Music]
[Applause]